[Music]
[音乐]
我将解释如何制作一个
I'm going to explain how to make a
圣诞树，当我们
要做的很简单
I'm going to explain how to make a
Christmas tree Christmas card when we're
这个，但是在我解释之前，我只是
要度过一些圣诞节
Christmas tree Christmas card when we're
going to make is very simple looks like
书中的树木
很复杂，我会告诉你
going to make is very simple looks like
this but before I explain it I'm just
教程参考了它们，因此如果您愿意
自己弄清楚怎么做
this but before I explain it I'm just
going to run through some Christmas
可以去，所以我要开始
基思更多的喙哦，没有圣诞老人和他的
going to run through some Christmas
trees in books that are quite
圣诞树是这个相当的
复杂而令人愉悦的设计
trees in books that are quite
complicated and I'll tell you which
基于这里的平行折叠
教程六，然后还有很多
complicated and I'll tell you which
tutorials refer to them so if you want
教程11的插槽数量
看着它就可以了
tutorials refer to them so if you want
to work out how to do it yourself you
它实际上是如何工作的
我认为这确实是复杂的设计
to work out how to do it yourself you
can have a go so I'm gonna start with
真的很可能是最好的
我将向他展示整个教程
can have a go so I'm gonna start with
Keith's more beak oh no Santa and his
无论如何这是关键的小喙哦，不，圣诞老人
我要告诉你的第二个是12
Keith's more beak oh no Santa and his
Christmas tree is this one quite a
罗伯茨·奥布达（Robertsóbuda）的圣诞节这一天
在后面是一个有趣的人
Christmas tree is this one quite a
complicated very pleasing design it's
在这个襟翼下，因为它不是
实际上是一棵树，有点
complicated very pleasing design it's
based on a parallel fold here which is
和碎片，这是一个可爱的
角度默认值这些主要位是尖锐的
based on a parallel fold here which is
tutorial six and then there's also a lot
角度默认值几乎保持不变
当页面放平，然后他们已经
tutorial six and then there's also a lot
of slots which are tutorial 11 maybe
每个末端只有3d小块
叶子全部贴在您的页面上
of slots which are tutorial 11 maybe
looking at it end on you can get an idea
把那些卡在里面，所以他们给这些
多余的零件，这样可以锐角化
looking at it end on you can get an idea
of how it actually works this is quite a
本教程也是如此
和添加的3d小片段
of how it actually works this is quite a
complicated design I think it's really
教程八，那是第二个
第三个是胡桃夹子，这是
complicated design I think it's really
really pleasing possibly the best one
尼克·丹奇（Nick Dench）的作品，他有一个非常
好奇的一种实心树是
really pleasing possibly the best one
I'll be showing him the whole tutorial
基于扭曲机制提高了
金字塔上的变化非常令人愉悦
I'll be showing him the whole tutorial
anyway that's key small beak oh no Santa
真的非常依赖所有
整个插图
anyway that's key small beak oh no Santa
second one I want to show you is the 12
扭转机制是教程
十七岁和金字塔这是一个
second one I want to show you is the 12
days of Christmas by Roberts óbuda this
本教程的金字塔变体
我要告诉你的最后一本书是21
days of Christmas by Roberts óbuda this
is an intriguing one at the back here
再次是另一个《胡桃夹子》
由帕特里夏·弗雷（Patricia Frey）设计，树就在这里
is an intriguing one at the back here
under this flap because it's not
这是一个不错的七，我认为
一棵漂亮的树，这棵树是基于
under this flap because it's not
actually a tree it's sort of the bits
这是一个锐角默认教程
提高平行四边形教程五
actually a tree it's sort of the bits
and pieces on it and this one is a cute
以及浮动平面变化教程
十二
and pieces on it and this one is a cute
angle defaults these main bits are acute
所以我只解释一下
从后面看，您可以看到这个主要
angle defaults these main bits are acute
angle defaults that pretty much go flat
它的主体是锐角视图
折叠这块来这里提高
angle defaults that pretty much go flat
when the page goes flat and then they've
这是水上飞机，然后
如果你从侧面看
when the page goes flat and then they've
got little 3d pieces at each end where
可以看到所有这些业务，这就是全部
平行四边形出现
got little 3d pieces at each end where
the leaf all sticks to the page you've
角度google我要显示的最后一个
你我真的不会做
the leaf all sticks to the page you've
got those stuck in so they give these
这是圣诞节吗
卡，我认为它来自
got those stuck in so they give these
extra pieces so sebou de the acute angle
华盛顿的史密森尼博物馆，我看不到
实际上作为弹出卡是纸
extra pieces so sebou de the acute angle
V for this tutorial too
确实可以折叠的雕塑
不是基于基础，而是全部基于
V for this tutorial too
and the adding small 3d pieces this
插槽和污渍教程11，然后
这是我们的螺旋式教程10
and the adding small 3d pieces this
tutorial eight so that's the second one
现在转到我要展示的那个
你如何做到这一点，因为
tutorial eight so that's the second one
the third one is the Nutcracker this is
它是如此简单，实际上，如果
你为很多人制作了很多卡片
the third one is the Nutcracker this is
by Nick Dench fields and he's got a very
你的朋友，你可以打开这个
轻松快捷地出门
by Nick Dench fields and he's got a very
curious one kind of a solid tree this is
所以我们需要一个基础
牧师真的很彻底，所以当你
curious one kind of a solid tree this is
based on a twisting mechanism raising a
将页面平放在桌子上
放平这将是树
based on a twisting mechanism raising a
variation on the pyramid quite pleasing
再次将它对折
将它对折，然后对折
variation on the pyramid quite pleasing
really relies a lot on the all the
您想要的树的类型的角度
如果您想要很多，您会深蹲或
really relies a lot on the all the
illustration all over the surfaces of it
你可以跟随的更广泛的
这是一个不同的角度，所以
illustration all over the surfaces of it
the twisting mechanism is tutorial
这次我们要得到的是
如果你现在在这里和现在都腾空了
the twisting mechanism is tutorial
seventeen and the pyramid it's a
看看这个，我已经三分了
层，但不必是你
seventeen and the pyramid it's a
variation of the pyramid that's tutorial
可以使它变得更复杂
有四五六层
variation of the pyramid that's tutorial
21 last book I'm going to show you is
你喜欢我要和三个一起去
再次如此，这是相当快捷和容易的
21 last book I'm going to show you is
again it's another The Nutcracker
首先将它分成三个部分
每节第一节和第二节
again it's another The Nutcracker
by Patricia Frey and the tree is here
三个他们都有了角度
折到中央折痕是一样的
by Patricia Frey and the tree is here
this is quite a nice seven I think it's
在所有三个上，但它们重叠，所以顶部
一层与下一层重叠，
this is quite a nice seven I think it's
a pretty good tree and this one is based
与下一个重叠，因此您实际上需要
重新折叠它们，以便下一个可以
a pretty good tree and this one is based
on it's an acute angle default tutorial
容纳它下面的一个
这将是最底层
on it's an acute angle default tutorial
to raising parallelograms tutorial five
我们将把它折成相同的
角度，但你知道再说
to raising parallelograms tutorial five
and a floating plane variation tutorial
厘米在这厘米
将会是我将要讨论的最底层的
and a floating plane variation tutorial
twelve
剪掉那些标签，剪掉那一块，等等
这将适合这里
twelve
so I'll just explain those if you look
可以放在这里，所以我们可以将其粘贴
关于这里看起来正确
so I'll just explain those if you look
at it from behind you can see this main
如您所见，这将变得平坦
页面平坦时，树是平坦的
at it from behind you can see this main
body of it this is the acute angle view
它站在我们的壁炉架上
是的，它在维度上
body of it this is the acute angle view
fold this piece coming up here to raise
3d树，因此我们将从此开始
如果我要放标签
fold this piece coming up here to raise
this this is the floating plane and then
在下面，但实际上您可以
让他们侧身伸出来
this this is the floating plane and then
if you look at it from the side here you
如果您在树上有更自由的边缘
要它放平，我可以粘
if you look at it from the side here you
can see all these business this is all
这两个标签同时显示
只需再次检查该位置
can see all these business this is all
the parallelograms coming up the acute
去那里
对齐弹出窗口上的中央折痕
the parallelograms coming up the acute
angle google the last one I want to show
中央的折痕就在那里
确保第二个可以正常工作
angle google the last one I want to show
you that I'm not actually going to make
将会再次重叠
我们需要以相同角度折叠
you that I'm not actually going to make
is this one this is from a Christmas
但不要像
前一个，所以最后一个进来
is this one this is from a Christmas
card I think it came from the
大约一厘米，所以我要走
把它放在半厘米左右
card I think it came from the
Smithsonian in Washington I don't see it
所以带来了少量
我会一遍又一遍地剪掉两个标签
Smithsonian in Washington I don't see it
actually as a pop-up card it is a paper
您需要在这里做的另一件事
因为它会重叠它
actually as a pop-up card it is a paper
sculpture that does fold flat but it
这里需要切掉一点
选项卡的将与树的部分冲突
sculpture that does fold flat but it
isn't on a base and it's all based on
在它下面，所以我们实际上将起飞
一块
isn't on a base and it's all based on
slots and smuts a tutorial 11 and then
说折下那些，这应该
能够放在上面
slots and smuts a tutorial 11 and then
there's this spiral tutorial 10 we will
很舒服，你需要排队
弹出框的中央折痕
there's this spiral tutorial 10 we will
now move on to the one I'm going to show
在页面上出现中央折痕
那是第二，我们将尝试关闭
now move on to the one I'm going to show
you how to make that's this one because
确保它仍然有效
我们去那里，然后第三个
you how to make that's this one because
it's so simple you could actually if
根本不需要重新折叠它，但是我们
仍然需要在
it's so simple you could actually if
you're making a lot of cards for a lot
底部，所以它可以重叠
也令人满意地在顶部
you're making a lot of cards for a lot
of your friends you can just turn this
我们将它们折叠在这两个标签下
会发生冲突，所以我只剪一个
of your friends you can just turn this
one out quite easily and quite quickly
只是在那里，所以那里没有
将会是一个问题，这里我们需要
one out quite easily and quite quickly
so we'll need a base there's a base
一次又一次地减少刺激
可以将胶水放在两个标签上
so we'll need a base there's a base
priests really thoroughly so when you
同时
然后将中央折痕与
priests really thoroughly so when you
lay the page flat on the table it just
基卡的中央折痕重叠
它下面有一些树，我们
lay the page flat on the table it just
goes flat this is going to be the tree
走
一切都很好，现在
goes flat this is going to be the tree
so again it's it's been folded in half
看起来使我们的桌子保持最新
底部，所以这只是一个普通的
so again it's it's been folded in half
you fold it in half and then you fold
平行折叠是一张卡片
三个平行折痕
you fold it in half and then you fold
the angle the type of tree you want so
也可以粘在那里
只需在两个标签上贴上胶水，
the angle the type of tree you want so
if you wanted a much you know squat or
再次，您将中央折痕对齐
随着基地的中央折痕
if you wanted a much you know squat or
wider one you could you could follow
在树下有点是这
圣诞树看起来最好
wider one you could you could follow
this as a different angle and so that's
像站在壁炉架上一样
这样就在3D中，但您可以全力以赴
this as a different angle and so that's
what we've got this time I'll just cut
平坦的方式，然后由您决定
装饰它，你可以在上面放星星
what we've got this time I'll just cut
all this spare off here and now if you
可以在上面放泡泡你可以放任何东西
上面有贴纸的照片
all this spare off here and now if you
look at this I've done it in three
蜡烛任何你喜欢的取决于你
在这种情况下，这就是你的设计
look at this I've done it in three
layers but it doesn't have to be you
放一点粗切的培根
油
layers but it doesn't have to be you
could make it a more complicated tree
只是银箔带给我们一些
闪闪发光，如果我做的很好
could make it a more complicated tree
with it four five six as many layers as
一个朋友可能我把
页面其余部分都闪闪发光
with it four five six as many layers as
you like I'm going to go with three
也是如此，这很简单
快速圣诞贺卡弹出
you like I'm going to go with three
again just so it's fairly quick and easy
[音乐]
[掌声]
again just so it's fairly quick and easy
to make start by cutting it into three
[音乐]